Amanda Sealshaw, it is time for the Big Up Let Down.
All right, our Big Up goes to a Cartier website employee's last day on the job.
Rogelio Villarreal, a 27-year-old from Mexico, discovered Cartier earrings priced at $14.
Whoa.
Instead of $14,000 on their website.
Snatched them up like they were the last seats at a Sunday brunch, okay?
After realizing the mistake, Cartier tried to cancel Rogelio's order.
He was like, nah, nah, tan bueno.
Cartier then jacked the price back up to $14,000 and tried to cancel the order.
Rogelio filed a complaint with the branch of the Federal Consumer Protection Agency,
and Cartier had to come up off them $14,000 earrings.
Well, let me take it up a notch.
He bought two pairs.
One for him and one for his mama.
Happy Mother's Day!
Today's...
Let down.
Oh, my God.
Goes to playing Candy Crush in bad faith.
Reverend Lawrence Kozak spent $40,000 of the church's money on games like Mario Kart and
Candy Crush.
I'm going to tell you now, as an avid Candy Crusher, if you're spending 40 racks on Candy
Crush, all that means is you suck at Candy Crush.
He was actually arrested.
What?
He was arrested.
Yes, he was arrested, and he had to fork over $250,000 bail, which I'm sure he pulled from
the same fund.
So, shout out to the congregation.
Hallelujah!
We are, we are, we are.